<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anthony Oduor</title>
    <description>Web Developer from Earth</description>
    <link></link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>HAME R1 router WIFI password</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hamer1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently picked up - HAME R1 Portable 4400mAh Battery Powered 3G - off &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ebay.com/sch/i.html?_from=R40&amp;amp;_trksid=p2047675.m570.l1313.TR0.TRC0.H0.XHAME+R1+router&amp;amp;_nkw=HAME+R1+router&amp;amp;_sacat=0&quot;&gt;ebay&lt;/a&gt;. The item is advertised as &lt;em&gt;Wireless Router WIFI Router R1 3 in 1&lt;/em&gt;. As it happens, the seller repackages the item so that they can ship more like a gift than a purchased product. Which is thoughtful but can end up forgetting a few things. In my case, the HAME comes with individual default password just below the default SSID at the back of the device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mine wasn&amp;#39;t there. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hametech.com/html/product/&quot;&gt;Hametech&lt;/a&gt;, the english website of the manufacturer is most useless as the support pages are long dead... Frustrated by the seller (By now, 4 messages sent to the seller via Skype, Ebay and Email) and now by the manufacturer; I resorted to youtube to see if I can find any HAME unboxings that will help or someone with such a problem in the comments section. Bupkis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hmmm, but as I was watching the videos, I made an observation regarding the WIFI passsword, there was a pattern. I picked up a similarity on the initial characters as they typed the password. The first 3 characters were always the same i.e. started with 7c3. The default password uses WPA encryption so the password has to have a minimum of 8 characters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also made a visual connection between the default SSID written at the back of the device as they typed. Hame SSID is in the format &lt;strong&gt;HAME&lt;em&gt;R1&lt;/em&gt;xxxx&lt;/strong&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;xxxx&lt;/strong&gt; being the unique set of characters with each device. So if your device had SSID &lt;strong&gt;HAME&lt;em&gt;R1&lt;/em&gt;x123&lt;/strong&gt;, then you extract the characters after the last underscore and append them to 7c3. You end up with &lt;strong&gt;7c3x123&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You still won&amp;#39;t be able to connect as most devices validate password to meet the minimum no. of characters before allowing you to connect at all. I went back to two of the videos I had watched and as fate would have it, they both ended with 8 as the final character of the WIFI password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So your working password (based on the above deductions) should be &lt;strong&gt;7c3x1238&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you stare at the format a for minute and analyse it. There are 7 characters before the last one. The last character is a number 8, the first is 7. The third character is always 3. The second is always c.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Youtube Videos: 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9NwZI5jEbNI&quot;&gt;ộ phát wifi hame r1&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z73NNcyo9yl&quot;&gt;HAME MPR-A1 Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a good introduction on HAME routers. See &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.3ptechies.com/it-support/networking/hame-3g-wi-fi-modem-review-manual-settings-english.html&quot;&gt;Hame 3G Wi-Fi Modem – Review, Manual Settings for Non Chinese Users&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>/hame-r1-router-wifi-password/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/hame-r1-router-wifi-password/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>